# WIKTORIA SAWICKA

I graduated from the Wroclaw University of Science and Technology with a Bachelor of Science in Architecture.

For a year I gathered experience in designing e-commerce stores. Currently I'm working at Capgemini where I am responsible for an innovative project for a bank. I am a passionate designer who loves working in a team, analyzing and finding solutions to user and client problems. I have an open mind and good communication skills, which makes me a good team member.

Check my portfolio! wsawicka.com

### CONTACT



wsawicka9855@gmail.com



+48 732 443 201

#### **EDUCATION**

2017-2021

Wrocław University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science in Architecture

## **LANGUAGE**

English, advanced Polish, native

#### **SKILLS**

- Graphic design
- User Interface design
- Usability testing
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (Data Protection Directive)

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **UX/UI DESIGNER**

Capgemini | from January 2022

- working with Business analysts, translating business requirements into mockups,
- working with developers: conducting handovers, performing design reviews
- presenting a demo to the clients
- working on user flow
- making the visual side of the project

#### **UX/UI DESIGNER**

Media Ambassador | from January 2021

- independdy working on the new Content Management System (CMS)
- creating mockups for online stores (Top Secret, Mlekolandia, MadamRock, Primodi, Fronero, Chicaca, BIG STAR, Qubus, Drogieria Jaśmin) for dekstop, tablet and mobile
- conducting client workshops
- creating logo and illustrations
- preparation of advertising banners for social media

# WHAT MORE?

UX/UI Designer | CodersCrew Association | 2019 - 2021

work on non-profit projects like CodersBoard, Material Design, participating in stages of CodersBoard project like: making up personas, user journey maps, user flows, information architecture, sketches/wireframes, usability tests, prototypes

#### 12/09/2020 - 13/09/2020

 Workshops and social hackathone "Sensorycznie i na serio" devoted to the issue of people with sensory disabilities

#### 29/03 - 02/04/2020

"Creative Coding" online course organized by The Awwwesomes